nobody wants to lose money on ads why
would you start a business to lose money
nobody would do that that's silly and
yet most people who run paid advertising
campaigns on Facebook Instagram Tik Tok
YouTube LinkedIn they lose a ton of cash
every single day and then they come to
me saying Jeremiah help save me help me
to not experience this anymore and
that's what I help people do and I've
been doing that for years is how to make
paid advertising produce professional
result results that work when the
Facebook ads platform popped up on the
scene I was one of the first users of
this generated close to a million dollar
just shy of it about
$750,000 in 2009 using Facebook ads and
since then I have gone on to help
coaches mentors and trainers generate
tens of millions of dollars using paid
advertising but here's the best part
you're like I don't got tens of millions
of dollars I don't got time and
experience like you do here's the thing
a lot of the people that I work with
most of them are just getting started
like you
are now here's the thing though and I
got to tell you this I said this in my
last
video you only want to spend how much
you're willing to lose when it comes to
paid ads and and you might be saying
well wait a sec jeremi I thought you
said we're going to talk about how to
not lose money of course nobody wants to
lose money but you have to go to the
table
deciding what you're willing to lose
with and and I liken this to gambling in
a way Facebook ads similar to the stock
market can be a form of gambling and for
most people it has all similar
returns but it's way more predictable
than the craps table blackjack or poker
to run Facebook ads or to trade stocks
if you actually know what you're doing
my mom mentors people on doing that I am
learning how to do the stock market but
I know how to do Facebook ads really
well okay so all that to say uh for
those of you who are wondering who is
this guy got his crazy Street PR shirt
on all this video game stuff looks like
he's in a teenager's bedroom who am I my
name is Jeremiah Kowski and I have been
helping business owners for the last 21
years exclusively full-time it's been my
main focus to scale their businesses and
Brands to reach millions of people from
zero and I have a system that is proven
to go from virtual obscurity nobody
knows who you are you don't have any
following you have no connections you
have no Financial reason resources even
to start with maybe very few Financial
Resources once you're running paid
ads to be able to scale a brand to
become a household name a industry
leader a category King as likened in in
in the book play bigger in your Niche
topic industry or realm and that's one
of the things the first things that I
tell everybody you have to
identify what realm your operating in
when we think about a realm I want you
to think about this like a kingdom okay
and and and for those of you that are
like Kingdom entrepreneurship no I
listen I'm a Christian I don't really
subscribe to the whole Kingdom
entrepreneurship thing don't crucify me
for that I just I I'm more of a
traditional business guy as far as that
goes but the realm concept if you think
about this is very important you have a
realm you have a lane have you ever
heard that stay in your lane I used to
really really resist the idea of staying
in my lane for years I didn't like it I
was like you know what I have so much to
offer people I have so much to put out
there I don't want to stay in my lane
and then uh through a journey of
struggle and uh my wife getting pregnant
and us having an incredible son and me
realizing okay I got to take this thing
seriously I'm 36 years old uh you know
might as well grow up a little bit
haven't fully grown up obviously as you
can tell I still play video games I
still love to do those things helps me
kind of get a little bit more creative
when it comes to creating content and
running Facebook ads to be honest I
actually think I'm more effective at
what I do today because of a lot of the
video games that I play and a lot of
when we look at how marketing works it's
likened to a game how many of you love
board games there's a there's a reason
why I'm talking about this related to
Facebook ads and I'm going to land This
Plane very quickly for you so that you
understand it have you ever played the
game Candyland or as I like to say you
know uh big pharma's uh indoctrination
campaign for being addicted to sugar for
life no but what I not not really but uh
The Game of Life is probably maybe a
little bit of a better concept as far as
this goes um you follow a path and
there's a starting point and there's
like a finishing Point as far as that
goes when you are running Facebook ads
you are moving people along a path step
by step and the first starting place is
going to be your Facebook ad where they
find you on an advertising campaign okay
so when somebody finds you on an ad
campaign this is like they roll the dice
and then they're like they're going to
go three spaces forward and then this
could be your uh ebook this could be
your mini course this could be your
webinar this could be your coaching
program straight up this could be a vssl
this could be a sales call this could be
a DM campaign or a messenger campaign by
the way how many of y'all have heard
about funnels that utilize
DMS uh sales calls uh webinars
challenges uh ebooks uh uh mini classes
micro webinars micro workshops all of
that stuff right guess what they all
work uh the problem is is this though is
that if you're trying to do all of these
things at once you're going to have a
bad time and you're going to go crash
and burn because you're going to be
distracted because you're not really
focused on your lane so you want to pick
one of those sort of funnel
Concepts to start testing your
initial office
with and this is what I Mentor people on
in my coaching program in what what we
call the client growth accelerator
program and this is not going to be a
sales pitch on here these videos are not
intended to be a sales pitch at all but
I'm just going to show you over at my
website jerem Kowski decom you can click
on group coaching program enrollment is
now closed you can jump on the waiting
list to my client growth accelerator
program which is a master mind we're
actually going to probably rename this
from coaching program to Mastermind
where we help you FasTrack yourself to
making six and seven figures with your
coaching or course or online business by
having an offer that works and that's
what I work with people on every single
day in my business and that's what I
have been doing pretty much exclusively
throughout my whole career successfully
might I add you have to have an offer of
some kind okay so back to the concept of
staying in your lane Candy Land The Game
of Life you start with an ad and it
moves people along a path and the
ultimate
goal along that
path
is sunshine and
rainbows no it's finances money and some
of you might be saying wait a sec no
it's not it's impact it's helping people
it's providing value it's giving good
products services to people listen of
course of
course what are they paying for they're
paying for something that is valuable
but the only reason that you are in
business and if we're talking about
running paid advertising campaigns we
have to talk about making money and I
meet a lot of people who say well
Jeremiah can you just stop it with that
money talk all the time and then they
want me to teach them paid advertising
I'm just like cuckoo I'm sorry but you
got to and maybe that I'm sorry if that
offended you a little bit but you got to
talk about making money if you're going
to be spending money in a campaign does
that make sense okay because we can't ex
we can't
expense finances in paid ads unless we
have income coming in to replace it and
this is one of the biggest mistakes that
I see that a lot of people make when it
comes to their paid advertisings they're
thinking about it all wrong they're
thinking about it from a concept of
being an expense well I don't want to
spend too much on ads over here I don't
want to you know like as if the money is
not going to come in or it's going to
come back to them like five years from
now that's the old way of doing business
the new way and the new school way of
doing business that we teach people that
I've been mentoring people on for years
is that you want to replace whatever you
are spending on ads within 30 to 60 days
max and my goal is always you want to
minimum
double to Triple the amount of money
you're spending on ads within 30 days
okay so like I want you to think about
it from that lens and that perspective
that you should not be running paid ads
campaigns unless okay let's say you
spend
$500 within four weeks you should be
making at least
a, to
$1,500 in sales okay and some of you
might be saying well Jeremiah that's not
that's not enough to live off of that's
not even worth it the juice isn't worth
the
squeeze it's not worth the effort for
that okay this is this is just a concept
this is just something to a a a
demonstration as far as that goes a lot
of our clients when they start to become
successful they actually don't just see
double and triple the results in their
ad spend but if you're like one of my
clients Sandy that we ran a campaign for
$110,000 in ad spend within 30 days
produced
$360,000 in sales that is over a
36 times return on that investment and
so if you could spend $110,000 on a
credit card most people can open a
credit card with $10,000 and this is why
I would recommend pay off your
debt pay off your consumer
debts so that you can increase your
credit limits because you don't want to
be spending cash to run your ads you
don't want to be cash strapped you want
to be spending credit to run your ads
and I'm going to be one of the first
people that you hear that tells you this
because most people don't want to tell
you something that might get you more
into debt if you don't know how to
manage your debt you got to be careful
with this of course and we have methods
that we teach when it comes to organic
and not spending money and things like
that maybe you're thinking I don't want
to spend any money on ads now listen
then this video is not for you the rest
of this video is only about spending
money on ads at this point go watch some
of our other videos if you're not
wanting to spend any money on ads for
the rest of you opening up the ability
to have Flex in your finances by having
some form of capital capital in the form
of say credit or credit cards of some
kind can be a great way to flex so that
then you might be able to spend $500 on
ads to test to see is a campaign working
or not to bring in those results but
what do you actually test with well
let's talk about that and I want to talk
about what's actually going to determine
the difference between you
making zero
or negative return returns right most
people that I meet a lot of people that
I meet in the beginning working with
them they have negative returns maybe
they've spent a lot of money on ads and
they've lost a lot of money has that
been your story I'm so sorry if that's
the
case but there's a difference between
the people who are making zero Returns
the people who are making 2 to 3x
returns I know quite a few of these
people right here and they're happy with
it but if you're like me I I I honestly
don't accept anything less than about an
eight eight times return on my ad ad
campaigns for every dollar that I spend
I need to bring in at least eight back
because that allows me to have the
finances that I need to pay for staff to
pay for the lifestyle that I want to
live and it allows me to create the
business that I want to create so what I
look for is between an eight to a the
best we've ever gotten is again a 36x
return right here okay that's the best
that I've gotten within 30
days within um about six months though
and and and by the way just those of
y'all that are preaching High ticket and
we're talking about high ticket there a
bit of there might be a longer lead in
time with that depends on what model
you're using as you optimize it you
could get Setters and closers and do so
very quickly within 30 days what we have
seen when it comes to maybe even using
High ticket as we have had upwards of 81
to 120 X return meaning for every dollar
we spend on ads we were able to bring in
$120 back within six months and that's
incredible and that's a true business
right there that's massively
capitalistic that is very profitable and
it's basically a license to print money
at that point but this takes a lot of
time I usually it's going to take you 18
to 36
months of testing to get get to this
point right here okay in my
experience most people don't have the
grit to get there and that's why most
people don't make seven and eight
figures in their business that's that's
what this level is is where for every
dollar spent maybe we spend a campaign
that's $10,000 and we make 1.2 million
off of that campaign and we've seen
those numbers happen but I want to just
make this practical for most of you
maybe you just want to make 5,000
10,000 $20,000 a month in your business
right something you can live off of
something that you can show to A lender
to buy a house in a metropolitan area in
the United States of America my wife and
I were able to buy this beautiful house
that we live in we have an incredible uh
luxurious Pool and Spa in our backyard
and we were able to purchase it with the
income from our
business because of doing this model
right here but the problem is that most
people are stuck at zero and I'm not
talking here to brag about my own life
because I want you to experience this
for your life as well but it's a pipe
dream for most people most people are
incapable of getting past this level
right
here and unfortunately that's most
people that are watching this video
right now you will watch this video and
you will still try to run ads and you
will never get past this point right
here why why your own choice it's your
own choice whether you get to here or
here or eventually to
here and maybe that's not what you want
to hear today maybe you want to blame
the algorithm maybe you want to blame a
coach that you had maybe you want to
blame a bad system no it's all about our
own choices and it boils down to one
thing and one thing only that
determines whether we get a return on
our ads and it's letting go of the fear
of other people's
opinions it's letting go of what other
people think about us trying to look
good all the time to everybody in our
life and perfectionism is the number one
reason why most people lose money on
their paid ads
campaigns that probably wasn't what you
thought I was going to say and I
understand that and it might be a
message that you are resisting right now
as I say it you may even check out log
off and never listen to a thing that I
say again because of that because it
challenges everything that you ever
thought you knew about life and business
but in my experience in 21 years looking
at thousands of business owners that
I've worked with the number one thing
that leads people to making zero when it
comes to their business and actually
being profitable with their ads is
always perfectionism it's always being
worried about people disliking them
having to do everything as they should
needing to follow best practices to a
tea all the time making their website
look fancy making all their branding
look good making their brand look
incredible presenting themselves in a
way that is extremely incredible as far
as that goes I'm sorry to say this that
produces
zzip zero when it comes
to your ads in fact it works against you
almost every single time and this this
is why most of the people that I meet
they just when they can't understand
this concept it's almost guaranteed I
can tell I'm like well you're not going
to make any
money and it's not that I'm a prophet of
Doom declaring that over them i' I'd
love to see them grow past this way of
thinking in order to be profitable maybe
you're a cut cut measure twice cut once
type of person maybe you're a planner
maybe you need to know how everything is
in front of you can I tell you this
running out is a risk of course it is
you're not going to always have
certainty as to how it it goes but one
of the most shest ways to make sure that
your ads actually work is to grow past
the need for other people's
approval because in fact what you're
looking for when it comes to running ad
campaigns is you're looking
for
disapproval far more often then you're
looking for approval and this might
sound counterintuitive and you may not
understand this right now I'm going to
explain it to you in as simple terms as
possible is that the only way that you
can actually get the algorithm on social
media to give you successful ads is
to
repel like a magnet you know when a
magnet pushes
away PE like the other magnet you need
to
repel and your campaign needs needs to
inspire and
incite
disapproval from the people who are the
most unlikely and how can we be so
arrogant to assume that they're unlikely
to spend money with us
well maybe from your perspective that is
arrogance and I understand and and and
and and you might be watching this right
now and and and and this is just this
this has rubbed you the wrong way I get
it can I encourage you to open your mind
to what will actually produce the result
that you're looking for and it might be
something that you have never heard
before you want your ads to show up in
front
of people that will spend money with you
most people who run ads their ads are
showing up in front of the wrong people
so they're spending all of this money on
ads to get their ad in front of people
that are never going to spend money with
them if I was selling hair care and I
was marketing it and all my ads kept
appearing in front
of men
with nice bald heads right I got I got
hair on my head I I'm I'm almost sort of
jealous sometimes of some guys they got
this they look really good bald I'm like
man you you look great dude but what if
you were running a hair care line and
you were running all your ads
to guys with bald
hair I'm sure they're great
people but you don't want your ad
running in front of them the problem is
that most people are creating their ads
campaigns in a way that ends up
targeting the wrong people and they do
so and it has nothing to do with the ads
manager at all it has everything to do
with how they communicate what they
actually do and deliver with their
product or service and this is where the
approval of other people part comes in
is because often times when I meet
people they're like well Jeremiah
clearly I'm not that silly
to run hair care to bald men of course
not like what who do you think I
[Music]
am okay of course not that was an
extreme example and maybe it was a bad
example as far as that goes but here's
what I see people do
often and it's actually a mistake that I
made in my
business so what I do is I help people
put together online campaigns using
Facebook ads to sell more of what they
sell online the problem is is if that's
how I described what I actually did to
people I would be attracting about 95%
of people that I don't actually want to
work with if I ran an ad campaign that
said hey want to run Facebook ads to
sell anything online I can show you how
95% of the people who would sign up for
that campaign would not be the people
that I want to work with and you might
be saying well Jeremiah you're turning
away good green money not all money that
is green is good you need to change that
thinking and realize that you want to
become very specific as to where you are
receiving the money from because if
you're try if you're desperate for money
just like a you know a teenage boy is
desperate for a a a prom date
unfortunately how I see a lot of
business owners today they act like a
teenage boy who is desperate to get the
to get the the hot date and he'll do
just about anything to get the attention
of somebody who's out
there that's not going to make you any
money and people can read the
desperation on you and they'll take
advantage of it and that's what most
coaches and mentors are doing is they're
saying I just want attention give me
some attention just look at me just and
they try to and they try to make
themselves more attractive on the
outward to get more
attention and it produces no results in
fact it hurts you more than anything
else when it comes to running ads the
most important part of making sure that
your ads don't lose
money has nothing to do with how you
look it has to do with the words that
you are
saying okay what you can actually do is
you can use your appearance to repel the
people that you don't want to work with
so for me I actually have designed my
set in order to repel the people that I
don't want to work with there's an
entire Market of coaches mentors and
trainers out there that will not want
anything to do with me because I play
video games they find it to be an
egregious divorce of discipline and it
shows a sign of a lack of
trustworthiness in me the fact that I
play video games according to them and
maybe you're watching this right now and
that's exactly what you're thinking
that is by Design on purpose because I
know that if that is the that is the
deep thought that somebody has about me
there is a 0% chance that I will be able
to close them or even help them produce
a result in their business because they
are more concerned with doing everything
perfect in life than actually getting
results and that's exactly what I'm
teaching you right here is you have to
get rid of your thoughts and Concepts
around perfectionism in order to make
things work work in this this dials
right into the words that we said so
what it is is your appearance often
times you want it to be more simple use
a very simple landing page something
that's not super fancy design your
graphics in canva all of my landing
pages in my website we use Squarespace I
use very simple photographs these are
old photos of me even right
here and I haven't updated them and yet
it still sells and makes us seven
figures here's a simple landing page
right here it's a photo of my wife and I
it's an outdated photo of us but you
know what it gets hundreds of people
every single month that opt in to get
these chat GPT prompts right here why
because it works and if I spent more
time and effort to make things look
better it would actually produce less
Financial returns for
me you have to understand that concept
you have to understand the concept that
putting so much energy into looking
Pro is a recipe for guaranteed loss when
it comes to your Facebook
ads most people for some reason they got
something deep inside of them that some
indoctrination by some voice that they
were educated by that has told them the
opposite of what I'm telling you right
now and they hold to it so tightly that
they would rather lose money than ever
look look less professional on the
internet my clients who actually trust
what I'm saying and start to apply it
and are willing to take a risk at at and
and I'm not talking about making your
character look bad I'm just talking
about not worrying so much about how you
look on the
outside and focusing more on what are
the words that you're saying and how are
you communicating these words and that's
what we love to use artificial
intelligence for to help us brainstorm
some of those words to help us
communicate better with our Target
client so what it is is there are words
that you put in your ad okay these are
written
words there are also words and generally
we love to run video ads there's words
that you say spoken in a video
ad you might also use a graphic ad that
has words on it the words that are
written the words that are spoken
and the words that are on a graphic
these are what
determine who the ad is shown
to about 30% of the equation okay the
other 70% of the equation and this is by
the way the part that most
people don't even look
at don't even spend time looking at they
avoid they make it the last thing that
they concern thems M eles with often
times it's the
words that are
on their landing
page the page that you're sending people
from the ad and you might say well
Jeremiah I don't really understand a lot
of Concepts when it comes to landing
pages I'm not really good at making them
look good and all that goes right back
to what I just told you in the beginning
here concerning yourself about making
your landing page look good is a
misappropriated focus on what is
actually effective when it comes to your
business and this is one of the services
that we have we actually provide people
over at my website over in my coaching
program as well as my oneon-one coaching
if you want to coach with me oneon-one
the the cost of this is $55,000 and we
work with you to put together your
landing page and make sure that your ads
are conver and make sure that things
work you know I've had a lot of people
they ask me Jeremiah can you just run my
ads for me and I look at their landing
page and I'm like well you're going have
to change this they're like well I'm not
going to change it I just need you to
run my ads and I tell them I'm not going
to help you unless I can do a whole
overhaul of your
messaging and
structure of your offer and
communication and so your offers
messaging and structure need to be
optimized for the type of person that
you're looking to reach and so this is
what matters more than anything else
when it comes to you running paid ads
making sure that they produce the best
result for you now there's a last part
of this that when you dial in your
landing page when you create that
structure and one of the best ways to
find the best structure that's out there
just go click on some other people's ads
on social media what if I cost them
money that's not how the Facebook ads
manage works it actually doesn't cost
them anything for you to go on Facebook
and click on people's ads I can
literally just scroll right here on my
social
media it's actually it's not showing me
any ads right now oh it's because I'm on
my page got to go to my profile here we
go so if I click on just any any old ad
have no idea who this is he's he's
teaching you how to get a bunch of Tik
Tok followers cool this is a landing
page right here if I click on another
landing page right here this shows me an
offer from somebody and so as you scroll
social media you can find offers from
different business owners that are out
there again I don't know who these
people are I'm literally just clicking
on the first ads that pop up on my
screen okay you can find offers that are
being ran in your Market there's a way
to actually tune the algorithm so that
your news feed starts to show you ads
from your competitors and so the idea is
this some of you are like oh I don't
want to copy my competitors this is why
you have to get over the worry and fear
of what other people think about you
people coming after you people not
liking what you're doing because at the
end of the day looking at what your
competitors are doing in their marketing
is one of the best things that you can
do it's called funnel hacking you're not
copying their
funnel by the way I encourage everybody
to just copy what I do if you want to be
successful please do in fact I I think
it's the best thing you can do is to
copy everything that I do and then just
change it for your offer but the best
way to know what works when it comes to
running ads is to look at what ads are
already being ran in the feed and then
to look at what ads your competitors are
running how are they structuring their
messaging how do they have the structure
of their funnel developed and then to
start to fill in the gaps rewrite a lot
of it you can use AI to help you rewrite
a lot of other landing pages that are
out there there's a whole I'll do a
whole training on that it would take me
like 40 minutes just to kind of show you
that side of things but that's how we
help develop and we work with our
clients every single day to develop the
best offers is by taking existing
funnels existing landing pages and then
filtering in their offers their
strategies their ideas into them and
then they start selling and they start
working and the people that I know that
actually make the most amount of money
this is what they do the ones who
struggle they're trying to be too
original because they're so concerned
about looking smart sounding smart
making people like them and pleasing
other people and when people pleasing is
your main priority in life you will lose
money with your
business you have to divorce the
approval of other people for you to be
able to succeed when it comes to being a
coach Mentor trainer and running
Facebook ads
online now there's a last part of this
that I can go into and and and and I
think it's important for me to just
touch on real briefly before we close
this video out is obviously getting
leads and getting people to sign up on a
landing page that's all great fine and
dandy but that's not going to turn into
sales for most people you have to sell
and you have to learn how to sell and
you have to learn how to communicate and
you have to learn how to use words to
get people to take action and to
exchange money with you that can happen
on a landing page that can also happen
in your email sequence that can happen
on a webinar that happens in your ebook
most of you are thinking about your
offers were all wrong you're focused on
providing value so that you look good to
everybody instead of realizing that your
offer does twofold not only does it
provide value but it is also a
promotional tool to be able to promote
what your best offers are and so if
you're not promoting your offers in all
of your content in all of the things
that they sign up for you are missing it
completely completely I meet people they
have books that they have poured hours
into and there's not even a mention of a
way to connect later or to buy a course
or to do anything in the book why
because they don't want to seem salesy I
don't want to look like one of those
people that's a fear of how you look to
other people that is stopping you from
being
successful manifested in most authors
that I
meet most people who launch a mini
course are terrified to even suggest
that somebody connect with them later in
another offer or to pay them money and
when you can challenge whatever that
thing is inside of you whatever you're
trying to avoid that is getting you to
not ask for the
sale to not ask people to take action
you know I
boldly mention to you that you can work
with me and get a VIP day for $55,000
and I am zero concerned if that offends
or repels anybody in fact I want it
to and I'm telling you to jump on the
waiting list for my coaching program to
work with me so that we can help upgrade
you to be able to make your ads to dial
in your messaging and to put all this
together where I get to jump in join
your team work with you help you craft
your sales messaging help you put
together your sales copy your landing
pages your offers your ads how you do
your sales pitch and all all of that
we're going to we got you covered we got
courses in there we got live trainings
we have hot seat events we have multiple
brand new things we're restructuring
even the members area to make it
literally a thousand times easier to
follow everything that we teach inside
of there we're not removing any of the
content but we're reorganizing it
literally this week we're putting it all
together so that it is so much simpler
to follow and to learn everything from
and that's why I encourage you to at
least jump on the waiting list for our
accelerator program
so that you don't have to go about this
on your own listen you could go about
this on your own totally I get it but I
think it would be better for you to join
and come along work with somebody like
me to come alongside you and hold your
hand along the way so get on the waiting
list for our accelerator program make
sure to subscribe to this channel we're
going to be posting a ton of videos here
coming up I'm excited to do this I did
this years ago where I was just doing a
bunch of live trainings like this for a
while and we're going to break down
Concepts and so if there's something
that you want me to teach
that you want to learn in these videos
and these live trainings and you want me
to break down for you leave it in the
comments below and I will go ahead and
we're we're going to start literally
building video content based on your
requests as far as that goes so I'm
excited to to to kind of turn this
YouTube channel into sort of your uh
your first step with working with me in
your business I do think whether you're
watching these YouTube videos or not
every single person if you've gotten to
this point the video needs to jump into
the accelerator needs to join the
waiting list for this but what we're
doing is we're turning this YouTube
channel into kind of the starting phase
for most people to get those foundations
established so that you can start to
make the kind of money that you want to
make so you can start to see the results
that you want and this concept right
here if you can start to understand this
that all roads lead to dialing in your
messaging and offer structure on your
landing
page this is what actually determines
whether your ads work or not
more than anything else it's 70% of the
equation and it has almost nothing to do
with the ads manager
targeting we use lookalike audiences to
Target our audience we use AI audiences
that actually find our audience for us
the artificial intelligence on Facebook
Instagram and all these paid platforms
are very intelligent at finding the
right people that should work with us
and that's what we work with you through
is how to dial that in in our
accelerator program so again make sure
keep watching these videos share it with
somebody and I'll see you on the next
one we'll talk soon